EVELYN SIMONS

CLIENT LIAISON OFFICER /ASPIRING SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

- 083 260 8649
- Parow, Cape Town
- in Evelyn Simons

EDUCATION

BAIN COMMUNICATIONS

UNISA (2012-2016)

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
COURSE - HYPERIONDEV (2020)

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN UDEMY (2020)

SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Contract Negotiation
- Problem solver
- Writing skills
- Quick learner
- Excel
- Microsoft Word
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Javascript
- Adobe XD
- UI/UX Fundamentals

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Accomplished Co-ordinator and Liaison officer with experience as a primary communications liaison for corporate executives. Dedicated Administrative Assistant and with experience in customer relations and managing challenges in busy environments. Proven ability to be decisive and make good judgments. Ambitious junior software engineer and excited to develop an in-depth understanding of software engineering under the direction of more

WORK EXPERIENCE

FUND / EX-GRATIA COORDINATOR

MMI Health | April 2013 - May 2018

- Prioritised, planned and scheduled all relevant meetings for both internal and external meetings.
- Ensured timeous preparation and dissemination of agendas, minutes and other relevant documentation.
- Coordinated ad hoc reports and communication to clients.
- Maintained accurate records of all the above mentioned documents and processes.
- Coordinated and provided professional service to schemes where special grants are awarded in cases where medical expenditure, in excess of the schemes available limits, has caused or would cause financial hardship for members.
- Negotiated with service providers for reduced/more cost effective quotes for proposed medical services in order to save the scheme money.
- Provided efficient and accurate investigations, administration and communication of all applications for added funding and queries.
- Provided efficient and accurate investigations, administration and communication of all Ex-Gratia applications and queries.

PROVIDER LIAISON OFFICER

Momentum | Jun 2018 - Nov 2019

- Handled incoming telephonic and email enquiries from providers/members/scheme and third parties.
- Dealt effectively with written enquiries by applying the knowledge of the industry, claims and any medical aid related enquiries.

ACHIEVEMENT

Company: Momentum (2019)

Momentum Health Annual Employee Nominee

INTERESTS

- Travelling
- Hiking
- Reading
- Coding

- Maintained and updated medical practice information.
- Captured and loaded provider and/or clinical data.
- Investigated and resolved claim enquiries.
- Kept record of all investigations in order to identify trends and areas for improvement within the business.
- Trained service providers on scheme rules and benefits.
- Participated in Provider engagement ad hoc projects as required.

IT ADMINISTRATOR

ICW CONSULTING | Present

- Created and transferred script files from pharmacies dispensing system via VPN/FTP or TV.
- Requested scripts from other vendors.
- Loaded script files into ICW System via claims loader.
- Generated monthly reports on time.
- Completed monthly reconciliations accurately and timeously.
- Generated ERA's and loaded them onto the client's system or FTP site.
- Communicated with management regarding the status of tasks and Month End processes.

REFERENCES

REFERENCE NAME

Fund Manager MMI Health, Bellville Abeeda English 072 269 6978

REFERENCE NAME

Team Manager Momentum, Bellville Marcelle Jaffer 0843062720